# HADI MOZAFFARI

Full stack web developer

Email: mozaffariTabar.h@gmail.com

**Phone:** +98-912-342-2599 **Address:** Tehran, IRAN

**LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/mozaffaritabar **GitHub:** github.com/mozaffariTabar

## **SUMMARY**

Experienced Full Stack Developer with more than sixteen years in the industry and high-level proficiency in the following languages: PHP, JavaScript, SQL, C, Python and some other modern frameworks like Laravel, React, GraphQL and etc. I am very familiar and experienced with Web Application Architecture (MVC, MVVM) and design patterns (GoF). I have worked with a good number of successful development teams.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **DEVOPS / MENTOR**

FitShape / IRAN / August 2018 - November 2019

- Build the company's internal new CMS panel with Html, Sass, ReactJs, NodeJs, MongoDB, GraphQL, Webpack by following design patterns.
- Test-Driven Development with ReactJs and Jest.
- Re-design the MySQL database with No-SQL / MongoDB and document that structure.
- Adding Redis db to speeding up the requests response.
- Teaching and mentoring some junior front-end developers.
- Transfer the company's projects to the version control system / Git.
- Participate in brainstorming sessions.

#### **SENIOR WED DEVELOPER**

Meraat / IRAN / July 2013 - July 2018

- Designing dedicated online Scrum app for the Company.
- Producing some internal software using PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass / CSS, HTML, RESTful API.
- Designing test cases and software test with PHPUnit.
- Designing and implementing MySQL / T-SQL database structure.
- Checking feasibility and evaluating required software and hardware for producing ordered software in multilayer (MVC) and object oriented (OOP).
- Participate in daily scrum sessions.
- Improve the UX / UI of the company's internal CRM / ERP panels.

## **HARD SKILLS**

Html / CSS / SASS / Bootstrap
Vanilla JavaScript
ReactJs / JQuery
Redux / Jest / Webpack
NodeJs / PHP / Laravel
Python / C / Design patterns
MySQL / MongoDB / Redis
RESTful / GraphQL / Express.js
AWS / Docker / Bash / Linux / Git

#### Familiar with:

Axios.js / Chart.js / ML5.js
P5.js / D3.js / Lodash.js
GitHub / GitLab / OOP / Slack
JSX / ES6 / Typescript / Babel
Adobe Photoshop / Illustrator
Adobe XD / Blender3D / Unity3D

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication / Lateral thinking
Time-management / Agility
Mind mapping / Teamwork

#### **LANGUAGES**

	WRITING	SPEAKING
PERSIAN	Native	Native
TURKISH	Native	Native
<b>ENGLISH</b>	Good	Good

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Science in Mechanical Engineering

University of Zanjan / 2007 - 2011

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering University of Zanjan / 2004 - 2007

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **SENIOR DEVELOPER / TEAM LEADER**

RanginPardaz / IRAN / June 2010 - June 2013

- Analyzing, interpreting and evaluating software demands, designing flowchart and providing technical production solutions
- Participating in meeting for evaluation and preparation of demands and cooperating for designing required module of system
- Designing, programming and troubleshooting store procedure and functions in MySQL databases
- Preparing web software using PHP, JavaScript, Html, CSS, JQuery
- Being senior programmer of web software production team using JavaScript programming language
- Testing and detecting bugs in program code and reforming them by standard protocols for software testing

## **JUNIOR / SENIOR PROGRAMMER**

CarinNow / IRAN / April 2002 - June 2010

- Participating in analysis and feasibility sessions for requested software, designing and producing it using PHP.
- Designing database and developing T-SQL Store Procedure for productive software.
- Testing, developing and maintaining produced software of company.
- Evaluating codes and comments and troubleshooting probable problems in produced software.
- Documentation of produced software for further usage.